[
  {
    "name": "JS",
    "questions": [
      {
        "value": 100,
        "question": "The mechanism that allows for a function call to be written before its declaration.",
        "answer": "hoisting"
      },
      {
        "value": 200,
        "question": "The context in which values are visible or can be referenced.",
        "answer": "scope"
      },
      {
        "value": 300,
        "question": "Template object that an object inherits methods and properties from.",
        "answer": "Prototype"
      },
      {
        "value": 400,
        "question": "The combination of a function with reference to its lexical environment.",
        "answer": "Closure"
      },
      {
        "value": 500,
        "question": "Data descriptor key that allows a property in an object to be changed with an assignment operator.",
        "answer": "writable"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "CS",
    "questions": [
      {
        "value": 100,
        "question": "A function or algorithm that calls itself one or more times until a specified condition is met.",
        "answer": "Recursion"
      },
      {
        "value": 200,
        "question": "Time required for a function to execute based on its input size.",
        "answer": "Time complexity"
      },

      {
        "value": 300,
        "question": "A form of automatic memory management which reclaims memory occupied by objects that are no longer in use by the program.",
        "answer": "Garbage collection"
      },
      {
        "value": 400,
        "question": "Optimization technique used primarily to speed up computer programs by storing the results of expensive function calls and returning the cached result when the same inputs occur again",
        "answer": "Memoization"
      },
      {
        "value": 500,
        "question": "In this data structure, for any given node C, if P is a parent node of C, then the key (the value) of P is greater than or equal to the key of C.",
        "answer": "Heap"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "BACKEND",
    "questions": [
      {
        "value": 100,
        "question": "Computer program or a device that provides functionality for other programs or devices, called \"clients\".",
        "answer": "Server"
      },
      {
        "value": 200,
        "question": "An application layer protocol for distributed, collaborative, hypermedia information systems.",
        "answer": "HTTP"
      },
      {
        "value": 300,
        "question": "A small piece of data sent from a website and stored on the user's computer by the user's web browser while the user is browsing.",
        "answer": "Cookie"
      },
      {
        "value": 400,
        "question": "Refers to the management of incremental, reversible changes and version control for relational database schemas.",
        "answer": "Schema migration"
      },
      {
        "value": 500,
        "question": "A device that acts as a reverse proxy and distributes network or application traffic across a number of servers.",
        "answer": "Load Balancer"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "FRONTEND",
    "questions": [
      {
        "value": 100,
        "question": "The API to a webpage, allowing programs to read and manipulate the page content, structure, and styles.",
        "answer": "DOM"
      },
      {
        "value": 200,
        "question": "Describes all HTML elements, and includes content, padding, border and margin.",
        "answer": "The CSS box model"
      },
      {
        "value": 300,
        "question": "Elements that clearly describe their meaning to both the browser and the developer, as well as providing enhanced accessibility.",
        "answer": "Semantic elements"
      },
      {
        "value": 400,
        "question": "A React hook which serves the same purpose as componentDidMount, componentDidUpdate, and componentWillUnmount did in class‚Äîbased React, but unified into a single API.",
        "answer": "useEffect"
      },
      {
        "value": 500,
        "question": "A JavaScript API for rendering interactive 2D and 3D graphics within any compatible web browser.",
        "answer": "WebGL"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "üçïüòà",
    "questions": [
      {
        "value": 999,
        "question": "The strength of the relationships between inter-dependent modules vs the degree to which the elements inside a module belong together.",
        "answer": "Coupling and cohesion"
      },
      {
        "value": 999,
        "question": "The process of injecting a function with number of prepared arguments in order to produce a subsequent function of lesser arity.",
        "answer": "Partial application"
      },
      {
        "value": 999,
        "question": "Style of programming that enables the instantiation of functions and data structures when their specified types are provided as parameters.",
        "answer": "Generic programming"
      },
      {
        "value": 999,
        "question": "Let q(x) be a property provable about objects x of type T. Then q(y) should be provable for objects y of type S where S is a subtype of T",
        "answer": "Liskov Substitution Principle"
      },
      {
        "value": 999,
        "question": "A system design principle that deals with the inter-relationships of components‚Äîa system should provide components that can be selected and assembled in various combinations to satisfy specific user requirements.",
        "answer": "Composability"
      }
    ]
  }
]
